

Profile

Senior Javascript developer with a systems engineering bachelor. I am a committed, self-taught, and dynamic person with excellent interpersonal relations and great teamwork capacity.

I have more than 9 years of experience working in Javascript Frontend/Backend projects.

Employment History

Web Developer, Logisoft Consulting SAS, Bogotá

SEPTEMBER 2013 - MARCH 2015

- Liferay Portets Development
- Javascript

Development Analyst, Ticxar SAS, Bogotá

MARCH 2015 - FEBRUARY 2017

- Liferay Portlets Development
- NodeJS Rest API Implementations.
- AngularJS and ReactJS Development.

FullStack Senior Developer, SmartSoft SA, Bogotá

FEBRUARY 2017 - DECEMBER 2017

Node JS Rest API and ReactJS Development

Web Developer, Jobsity, Bogotá

DECEMBER 2017 - FEBRUARY 2022

React Native, React JS, Angular 2+, NodeJS Development and Devops.

Leading the Development Team which owns 3 JS projects where i was in charge of:

- ReactJS + Typescript features creation.
- Maintain and improve the CI/CD process created by me (GitHub actions + AWS ECR/ AWS EB / AWS EKS)
- Create and maintain new GraphQL endpoints (Queries, Mutations and Subscriptions) on our NodeJS + Typescript Project.
- Create and maintain RestAPI endpoints

Frontend Engineer, Revelo, Bogotá

FEBRUARY 2022 - DECEMBER 2022

- React JS + Typescript Components creation and maintenance.
- Node JS Rest/Graphql implementations.
- Basic Golang Rest/Graphql Implementations

Education

Systems Engineer, Universidad Central de Colombia, Bogotá

JULY 2015 - NOVEMBER 2019

Details

+573204864976 andresfgonzalez.1988@gmail.com

Links

Linkedin

Skills

MySQL

Git

Docker

JavaScript

React JS

Node JS

HTML/CSS/JavaScript

GraphOL

React Native

Redux

TypeORM

TypeGraphQL

AWS

ExpressJS

Scrum

Angular 2+

Golang

Languages

English

Spanish